<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Favorite NBA Players</string>
    <string name="lebron_text">LeBron James (born December 30, 1984) is an American professional basketball player for the Los Angeles Lakers of the NBA.During his 17-year NBA career, James has played for the Cleveland Cavaliers, Miami Heat, and Los Angeles Lakers. He has competed in ten NBA Finals, including eight consecutive with the Heat and Cavaliers from 2011 through 2018. His accomplishments include four NBA championships, four NBA Most Valuable Player (MVP) Awards, four Finals MVP Awards, and two Olympic gold medals.</string>
    <string name="lebron_header">LeBron James</string>
    <string name="trae_text">Rayford Trae Young (born September 19, 1998) is an American professional basketball player for the Atlanta Hawks of the NBA. He played college basketball for the Oklahoma Sooners. In 2017, he tied the National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA) single-game assists record with 22. Young became the only player to ever lead the NCAA in both points and assists in a single season. He was drafted by the Dallas Mavericks in the 2018 NBA draft with the fifth pick, but was later traded to the Atlanta Hawks, along with a future first-round pick, for the draft rights to Luka Dončić.</string>
    <string name="trae_header">Trae Young</string>
    <string name="rose_text">Derrick Martell Rose (born October 4, 1988) is an American professional basketball player for the Detroit Pistons of the NBA. He played one year of college basketball for the Memphis Tigers before being drafted first overall by his hometown Chicago Bulls in the 2008 NBA draft. He was named the NBA Rookie of the Year and also became the youngest player to win the NBA Most Valuable Player Award in 2011 at age 22.</string>
    <string name="rose_header">Derrick Rose</string>
    <string name="jokic_header">Nikola Jokić</string>
    <string name="jokic_text">Nikola Jokić (born February 19, 1995) is a Serbian professional basketball player for the Denver Nuggets of the NBA. Standing at 7 ft 0 in (2.13 m), he plays in the center position. Jokić was selected by the Nuggets in the second round of the 2014 NBA draft. In the 2018–19 NBA season, while leading the Nuggets to the Conference Semifinals, he received his first All-Star and All-NBA First Team selections.</string>
    <string name="irving_text">Kyrie Andrew Irving (born March 23, 1992) is an American professional basketball player for the Brooklyn Nets of the NBA. He was named the Rookie of the Year after being selected by the Cleveland Cavaliers with the first overall pick in the 2011 NBA draft. A six-time All-Star and two-time member of the All-NBA Team, he won an NBA championship with the Cavaliers in 2016.</string>
    <string name="irving_header">Kyrie Irving</string>
</resources>